Guide to the Rice Alliance of Mental Health Awareness records, 2010-2016 UA 373
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice Alliance for Mental Health Awareness records
2010-2016
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University.
UA 373
0.25 Linear Feet (1 box)
This collection consists of minutes, club information, and events of the Rice Alliance for Mental Health Awareness club.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Aimee Nguyen and Anna Wehowsky donated materials in 2013 and 2016.
Accruals
Additional materials are expected for this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of minutes, club information, and events of the Rice Alliance for Mental Health Awareness club.
Biographical / Historical
Rice Alliance for Mental Health Awareness club, formerly called Active Minds, began at Rice in 2010. The organization acts as a peer resource on behalf of the Student Wellbeing Office. Their goal is to educate the student body about mental health issues.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; College students -- Texas; Health care and medicine
- Series I: Alphabetical Files
  - Chapter awards, 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mental Health Awareness Week, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 2014/2015 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 2015/2016 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National office information, 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Officer info, 2014/2015 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaire responses, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rice chapter information, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Social media, 2014/2015 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Well Being Week, 2014/2015 (Box 1, Folder 10)